<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
		<page id="bose_account_create_1"><item><topic>Why do I need to create an account?</topic><answer><![CDATA[<p>A SoundTouch<sup>&#174;</sup> account is required to keep track of your speakers, presets and music service. In addition, an account helps us better support your speaker and troubleshoot problems.</p> <p>If you are setting up multiple SoundTouch<sup>&#174;</sup> speakers, we strongly recommend that you set them up on the same SoundTouch<sup>&#174;</sup> account. Also, any time you install the SoundTouch<sup>&#174;</sup> app on another mobile device or computer, you are required to sign in using your SoundTouch<sup>&#174;</sup> account info.</p>]]></answer></item><item><topic>Why do I have to provide my email address?</topic><answer><![CDATA[<p>Each SoundTouch<sup>&#174;</sup> account is uniquely identified by an email address. Notifications of software and service updates are sent to this address. When you provide your email address, you can choose (or decline) to receive emails from Bose<sup>&#174;</sup> about new products, events and other announcements. Please read our privacy policy to learn more about how we use your email address by selecting <strong>Settings > About > LEGAL</strong>.</p> <p>If you prefer not to provide your email address, you can set up your speaker anonymously by providing a single-purpose or even non-working email address. In this case, your speaker will continue to receive system software updates, but you will not receive email notifications explaining the new features when these updates are available.</p>]]></answer></item><item><topic>Is there a minimum character or format requirement for the password?</topic><answer><![CDATA[<p>Your password must be at least six characters in length.&nbsp;The password field is case sensitive.</p>]]></answer></item><item><topic>Why should I provide my name and address?</topic><answer><![CDATA[<p>We use your name and address to improve your customer service experience should you need assistance. Please read our privacy policy to understand other ways we may use your name and address by selecting <strong>Settings > About > LEGAL.</strong></p>]]></answer></item></page>